{"data":[{"question":"If you drink like this, by midnight you _____ a gallon of beer!","a":"will drink","b":"will have drink","c":"will have drunk","d":"have drunk","answer":"3","explain":"\nFuture perfect: \n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future \n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP \n+ Sign word: by midnight ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of the month I'll ______ the book.","a":"have finished","b":"be finish","c":"be finished","d":"had finished","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of the month\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time you come we ______.","a":"will have finished","b":"will finish","c":"have finished","d":"be finished","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He'll he back at 2. I _____ by then.","a":"will finish","b":"will have finished","c":"will be finish","d":"will be finished","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by then (at 2)\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time you come, we _____ coffee.","a":"will have","b":"are having","c":"will have had","d":"have had","answer":"3","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By four o'clock, I ______ this book,","a":"will read","b":"will have read","c":"will be read","d":"have read","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by 4 o'clock\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We _____ this house off by 1999.","a":"will have paid","b":"will pay","c":"have paid","d":"will have pay","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect: \n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future \n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP \n+ Sign word: by 1999 ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time the doctor comes she will ______ all the temperatures.","a":"have look","b":"have taken","c":"be taken","d":"be took","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"They'll ______ by now","a":"arrive","b":"be arrived","c":"be arriving","d":"have arrived","answer":"4","explain":"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future \n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP \n+ Sign word: by now ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time the Newtons come we ______ waiting for half an hour.","a":"will be","b":"will have been","c":"will have","d":"have been","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}